chippewaboots.com 2019-06-04

# Justin Brands Privacy Policy

Justin Brands has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to our visitors' and customers' privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website.

* Personal and Non-Personal Information

When registering and/or making a purchase at our site, entering a contest, or responding to a survey, you may be asked to provide certain personally identifiable information about yourself, such as your name, email address, physical address, or telephone number.

We use personal information provided on order forms, such as a purchaser's name, email address, physical address, and credit card, to fulfill merchandise orders. We may also use order information to contact a purchaser when necessary, such as when a delivery may be delayed or when an ordered product is out of stock. Justin Brands may use personal information to notify consumers about new products or services. If we do, we will provide you with an email address by which you may inform us that you do not wish to receive such materials in the future. Justin Brands will only use and share your personal information as provided in this Privacy Policy, and will not share your personal information in any other manner without your permission, unless required by law.

We may also request non-personally identifiable information, such as annual income, buying preferences, or age, also known as demographic and profile data, though this information is optional. We may use this data to improve our site and enhance your shopping experience. For example, we may use this data to tailor your experience at our site, showing you Content that we think you might be interested in, and displaying Content according to your preferences. We may also share this information with others, such as advertisers interested in advertising on Justin Brands' Sites, in aggregate, anonymous form, which means that the information will not contain any personally identifiable information about you or any other person.

* Cookies

"Cookies" are pieces of information that are placed on an individual's computer hard drive to enable the individual to more easily communicate and interact with Justin Brands' sites. Justin Brands may use cookies to customize your shopping experience, to keep track of your shopping cart and to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We use cookies to deliver Content specific to your interests, to save your password (if you have registered with us) so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, and for other purposes. However, you may disallow cookies through your web browser and still shop on our Site. Justin Brands will never use cookies to retrieve information from a computer that is unrelated to Justin Brands' sites or your interaction with Justin Brands' sites.

* Internet Protocol (IP) Address

We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart for the duration of a session and to gather broad demographic information.

* Consent to Processing

By providing any personal information to this site, you fully understand and unambiguously consent to the collection and processing of such information in the United States or other locations where Justin Brands or its Support Vendors (as defined below) maintain facilities.

* Other Sites

Our site may contain links to other sites. Other sites may also reference or link to our site. Justin Brands is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other sites.

* Third-Party Technology and Data Collection

We may share your personal information with companies that provide support services to us (such as a printer, e-mail, mobile marketing, analytics providers, web hosting providers, call center service providers, sweepstakes vendors, payment processors, coupon delivery vendors, data enhancement, or fraud prevention providers) or that help us market our products and services (collectively, “Support Vendors”). These Support Vendors may need information about you in order to perform their functions (e.g., your name, email address, physical address, and credit card information, when needed to process a payment on Justin’s behalf). Your personal information may be stored and processed by these companies in the United States or other locations where these companies or Justin Brands maintain facilities. We require these Support Vendors to use best industry standards to keep your information secure, and importantly, these Support Vendors are not authorized to use the information we share with them for any purpose other than providing services on our behalf.

* Web Analytics

This site uses ClickTale web analytics service. ClickTale may record mouse clicks, mouse movements, scrolling activity as well as text you type in this website. This site does not use ClickTale to collect any personally identifiable information entered in this website. ClickTale does not track your browsing habits across web sites which do not use ClickTale services. For more information see Privacy Policy for Information Collected by the ClickTale Web Analytics Service. We are using the information collected by ClickTale service to enhance the usability of our website. You can choose to disable the Service at [ http://www.clicktale.net/disable.html ](http://www.clicktale.net/disable.html)

* Security

We take the security for all personal and non-personal information associated with our visitors and customers seriously. We use the encryption process, Secure Sockets Layering (SSL), to secure transmission of your order. Only those Justin Brands employees and Support Vendors who need access to your information in order to perform their duties are allowed access. Any employee or Support Vendor who violates our privacy and/or security policies may be subject to disciplinary action, including possible termination and civil and/or criminal prosecution.

* Choice/Opt-Out

If we ever send you information by email concerning new Justin Brands products or services, we will provide you with an email address by which you may request no future notices.

* Correct/Update

If you have registered with us, you may review your account information online for accuracy and make updates.

* Children’s Privacy

The Justin site is not directed towards, nor intended for users under the age of 13. Therefore, Justin does not knowingly request or solicit personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on the Justin site, make any purchases through the Justin site, use any of the interactive or public comment features of the Justin site or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address or any screen name or user name you may use. In the event that we receive actual knowledge that we have collected such personal information without the requisite and verifiable parental consent, we will delete that information from our database as quickly as is practical.

* California Privacy Rights

Justin currently does not disclose personal information of customers to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes.

* Your Acceptance of this Policy

By using this site, you signify your assent to our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this policy at any time. If we change the terms of this Privacy Policy, we will advise you by revising the “Last Updated” date at the top of this policy. Please check regularly for updated terms. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept these changes.
